The mission: survival
Solis is a action, adventure, science fiction film directed by Carl Strathie.
Following an accident, an Engineer of an asteroid mining company endures the extreme limits – both physical and
psychological – of human survival, trapped inside an escape pod as he helplessly idles towards the Sun.
Troy Holloway, played by Steven Ogg.
Commander Roberts, played by Alice Lowe.
Liz Holloway, played by Kate Coogan.
Ship / Suit Voice, played by Charlette Kilby.
Milton, played by Sid Phoenix.
Solis is a 2018 sci-fi survival film written and directed by Carl Strathie, and starring Steven Ogg; featured in
supporting voice roles are Alice Lowe, Sid Phoenix, Henry Douthwaite, Kate Coogan and Charlette Kilby.
The film was released in the United States on October 26, 2018.
The film explores themes of rescue, sun, trapped in
space, oxygen depletion, loss of son.
The tone is thought_provoking and mind_bending.